(Zack:)there's no
one right answer.
(Sheldon:)So...
(Leonard:)you and Zack again, huh?
(Penny:)Yeah, yeah, me
and Zack again.
(Zack:)Were we here earlier?
(Penny:)Okay, we should,
we should go.
(Zack:)Ah, not yet.
(Zack:)I want to talk science
with the science dudes.
(Howard:)Oh, and the science dudes want
to talk science with you.
(Howard:)What do you want
to talk about--
(Howard:)rocks, dinosaurs, our
friend the beaver?
(Zack:)You know, I saw this great thing
on the Discovery Channel.
(Zack:)Turns out
that if you kill a starfish,
(Zack:)it'll just come back to life.
(Sheldon:)Was the starfish
wearing boxer shorts?
(Sheldon:)Because you might have
been watching Nickelodeon.
(Zack:)No, I'm almost sure that
it was the Discovery Channel.
(Zack:)It was a great show.
(Zack:)They also said dolphins
might be smarter than people.
They might be smarter
than some people.
(Zack:)Maybe we can do an
experiment to find out.
(Sheldon:)That's easy enough.
(Sheldon:)We'd need a large tank of
water, a hoop to jump through,
(Sheldon:)and a bucket of whatever
bite-sized treats
(Sheldon:)you find tasty.
(Zack:)I don't get it.
(Leonard:)A dolphin might.
(Zack:)Oh, I see.
(Zack:)You guys are inferring
that I'm stupid.
(Sheldon:)That's not correct.
(Sheldon:)We were implying it.
(Sheldon:)You then inferred it.
(Zack:)Let's go.
(Penny:)You know, for a group of guys
(Penny:)who claim they spent most
of their lives being bullied,
(Penny:)you can be real jerks.
(Penny:)Shame on all of you.
(Raj:)What the hell did I do?
(Penny(Opens door again):)You laughed.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪